<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>YouTube Channels on Thneppel</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/youtube/</link>
    <description>Recent content in YouTube Channels on Thneppel</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Thiago Neppel</copyright>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/youtube/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Kim TV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/youtube/jimmykimtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/youtube/jimmykimtv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Edited over 27 YouTube videos for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@jimmykimtv&#34;&gt;Jimmy Kim TV&lt;/a&gt; in 2025, spanning travel vlogs, food reviews, and experience-based content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The editing workflow was centered in &lt;strong&gt;Adobe Premiere Pro&lt;/strong&gt;, making use of licensed stock footage and sound libraries, with selective application of third-party plugins to refine pacing, transitions, and overall polish.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Light motion graphics and minimal animations were produced in &lt;strong&gt;After Effects&lt;/strong&gt; when needed, supporting the narrative without distracting from the vlog-driven, authentic tone of the channel.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nice N Raw</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/youtube/nicenraw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/youtube/nicenraw/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Direction, content production, and video editing for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@NiceNRaw&#34;&gt;Nice N Raw&lt;/a&gt; YouTube channel, with responsibilities spanning creative direction, production planning, and post-production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The production workflow included on-set direction, camera operation, and coordination of audiovisual resources, ensuring visual coherence and a strong narrative foundation across episodes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Editing was primarily handled in &lt;strong&gt;Adobe Premiere Pro&lt;/strong&gt;, with extensive integration of &lt;strong&gt;After Effects&lt;/strong&gt; for motion graphics, visual enhancements, and animated elements that played a significant role in the channel’s visual identity. Licensed stock footage, sound libraries, and third-party plugins were used to refine pacing, transitions, and overall polish.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
